[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：所以第三幕，功能终极。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So Act III, function the ultimate.
你一直在想我们什么时候才能说到好的部分，对吧？
You've been wondering when are we gonna get to the good parts, right?
因为到目前为止一切都很可怕，对吧？
Because everything's been pretty horrible up until now, right?
这不是有点悲剧吗？
Hasn't this been kind of tragic?
所以我们会找到一些好的部分
So we're gonna get to some good parts and
JavaScript中好的部分都围绕着函数。
the good parts in JavaScript all wrap around the function.
函数真的是一些功能强大的东西。
Functions are really powerful bits of stuff.
在其他语言中，您将拥有方法、类、构造函数和模块。
In other languages, you'll have methods, classes, constructors, modules.
在JavaScript中，您所需要的就是函数。
In JavaScript all you need is functions.
功能太强大了。
Functions are so powerful.
他们可以做所有这些事情的工作，甚至更多。
They can do the work of all of those things and more.
他们只是在为建造东西提供一种通用的东西。
They're just serving a universal stuff for building things.
我们使用函数表达式或函数文字来构造函数。
We make functions using the function expression or function literal.
它将返回一个新的Function对象，然后可以调用该对象。
It would return a new function object, which could then be invoked.
函数表达式以单词function开头。
A function expression starts with the word function.
然后它可以采用一个可选的名称，
It can then take an optional name,
这允许您递归调用函数。
which allows you to call the function recursively.
它还允许记录代码和堆栈跟踪等内容。
It also allows for documenting things like a code and stack traces.
你给它传递参数，
You pass it parameters,
这是一组用逗号分隔的名称，用括号括起来。
which are a set of names separated by commas wrapped in parens.
它需要一个身体，这是一块用大括号包着的木块。
And it takes a body, which is a block wrapped in curly braces.
函数表达式生成函数对象的实例。
A function expression produces an instance of a function object.
每次对表达式求值时
And every time that expression gets evaluated
您将获得一个新的函数对象。
you'll get a new function object.
函数对象是第一类，
Function objects are first class,
这意味着它们可以作为参数传递给函数。
which means they can be passed as arguments to functions.
它们可以从函数返回，可以为它们赋值一个变量，并且
They can be returned from functions, they may be assigned a variables, and
它们可以存储在对象和数组中。
they may be stored in objects and arrays.
这与语言中的函数有很大的不同
This is very different than in languages where functions are sort of
静态的东西，只是在程序开始之前就存在了。
the static things, which just kind of exist before the program starts.
在JavaScript中，
In JavaScript,
函数运行并在编译时向环境中添加内容。
the functions run and add things to the environment as they're compiled.
而且因为函数是对象，所以它们是从函数而不是原型继承的。
And because functions are objects they inherit from function not prototype.
我们使用var语句声明和初始化函数中的变量。
We use the var statement to declare and initialize variables within functions.
没有在var语句中指定类型。
You don't specify a type in the var statement.
它可以接受任何类型。
It can accept any type.
函数中任何地方声明的变量都是可见的
And variables declared anywhere within a function are visible
函数中的任何地方。
everywhere within the function.
所以我们没有var语句的块作用域，我们只有函数作用域。
So we don't have block scope with the var statement we only have function scope.
因此，var语句做了一件非常奇怪的事情，它被分成两部分。
So, the var statement is does a really weird thing, it gets split into two parts.
声明部分被提升到函数的顶部，其中变量
The declaration part gets hoisted to the top of the function where the variable
使用undefined初始化。
gets initialized with undefined.
初始化部分变成普通赋值语句。
And the initialization part turns into an ordinary assignment statement.
这里我们得到var myVar=0，var myVar=
So here we've got var myVar = 0, var myVar =
Undefined被提升到函数的顶部。
undefined gets hoisted to the top of the function.
在看到最初的陈述时，
And at the sight of the original statement,
我们得到一个普通的赋值语句，它进行初始化。
we get an ordinary assignment statement, which does initialization.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：为了让事情更复杂，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: To make things more complicated,
JavaScript具有函数语句或函数声明。
JavaScript has a function statement or a function declaration.
不幸的是，它看起来与函数表达式完全相同。
Which unfortunately looks exactly like the function expression.
它以单词function开头，在这种情况下，名称是必需的。
It starts with the word function in this case the name is mandatory.
你不能忽略它。
You can't leave it out.
它采用相同的参数和相同的身体。
It takes the same parameters and takes the same body.
所以看起来和另一个一模一样。
So it looks exactly like the other one.
function语句是具有函数值的var语句的简写。
The function statement is a shorthand for a var statement with a function value.
所以函数foo展开为var foo=函数foo。
So function foo expands into var foo = function foo.
并且由于提升到var foo=undefined和
And that further expands because of hoisting into var foo = undefined and
foo=函数foo。
foo = function foo.
这两个函数现在都被提升到函数的顶部。
Both of these now get hoisted to the top of the function.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：正是因为这个第二次提升，语言才会这样做
&gt;&gt; Douglas: It's because of this second hoisting that the language does
不允许您在if内声明函数。
not allow you to declare a function inside of an if.
因为函数变量的赋值将被拉出
Because the assignment of the function variable is going to be pulled
从f移到了顶端，所以这是非法的。
out of the f and moved to the top, so that's illegal.
现在看来，大多数JavaScript引擎都允许您这样做。
Now it turns out most of the JavaScript engines allow you to do it anyway.
但因为标准说你不能
But because the standard says you can't,
他们对它的实际含义都有不同的看法。
they all have different opinions on what it actually means.
我不建议这样做。
I don't recommend doing that.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：所以既有函数表达式又有函数表达式真的很混乱
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So it's really confusing having both function expressions and
函数语句，两者看起来完全相同。
function statements, which both look exactly the same.
那你怎么区分它们？
So how do you tell them apart?
这取决于你在哪里。
And it depends on where you are.
如果语句的第一个标记是Function，则它是Function语句。
If the first token of a statement is function, then it is a function statement.
如果function这个词出现在其他任何地方，它就是一个函数声明。
If the word function occurs anyplace else, it's a function declaration.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：我们今天早上谈到了范围，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So we talked this morning about scope,
关于块作用域和函数作用域。
about block scope versus function scope.
块作用域是一个非常常见的东西，函数作用域是一个非常不寻常的东西，
And block scope is a very common thing, function scope is a very unusual thing,
这是JavaScript的var语句所特有的。
which is unique to JavaScript's var statement.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：因此，函数范围是足够的，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So and function scope is sufficient,
但是函数作用域看起来像块作用域。
but function scope looks like block scope.
或者至少语法与块范围语言相同，因此
Or at least the syntax is the same as block scope languages and so
你会感到困惑。
you get confusion.
所以在一些有块作用域的语言中，你可以做这样的蠢事。
So In some languages that have block scope, you can do stupid things like this.
其中可以有两个使用相同变量名的循环
Where you can have two loops both using the same variable name
作为他们的诱导变量。
as their induction variable.
它起作用是因为在这些语言中，每一种语言都将是不同的
And it works because in those languages, each of these will be in a different
范围，因此它们不会相互干扰。
scope, and so they won't interfere with each other.
这是极其不明智的，但却是合法的。
It's extremely unwise but legal.
在JavaScript中它也是非法的，但是
In JavaScript it is also illegal, but
这比不明智还糟糕，因为这里只创建了一个i变量。
it's worse than unwise because there's only one i variable created here.
两个循环将使用相同的i变量。
Both loops will be using the same i variable.
所以他们会互相干扰得很厉害
And so they will interfere with each other really badly and
此循环永远不会正确执行。
this loop will never correctly perform.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：那是因为所有东西都被提升到顶部。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That's because everything gets hoisted into the top.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：这是因为var声明都被提升到顶部，并且
&gt;&gt; Douglas: It's because both var declarations gets hoisted to the top and
没有检查变量是否已经声明。
there's no check to see if a variable has already been declared.
因此，如果有第二个var声明
So if there is a second var declaration for
同名好，这就是双好。
the same name good, that's double good.
这应该是个错误，但是
It should be an error, but
它不是，因为它不是一个错误会陷入麻烦。
it's not, because it's not an error can get into trouble.
因此，由于所有这些奇怪之处，我建议您清除所有变量
So because of all of this weirdness I recommend to clear all of your variables
在函数的顶部。
at the top of the function.
因为那就是他们实际被宣布的地方
Because that's where they're actually being declared and
在调用所有函数之前还要声明它们。
also declare all of your functions before you call them.
所有这些吊装废话都是专门制造出来的
All of this hoisting nonsense was created specifically so
你不需要这样做，你可以在函数被声明之前调用它。
that you don't have to do that, that you can call a function before it's declared.
但这就要求所有这些吊装的怪异
But that requires that all this hoisting weirdness be going on and
你知道主机在做什么。
that you understand what the hosting is doing.
我认为这对阅读你的节目的人期望太高了。
And I think that's too much to expect of the people reading your program.
因此，相反，我认为在调用函数之前声明函数要好得多。
So instead I think it's much better to say declare the function before you call it.
这是一件容易理解的事情。
That's a much easier thing to understand.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：但是Call，你使用的是Call这个词，我会称之为定义。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: But call, you're using the word call where I would call it defining.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：在JavaScript中，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: In JavaScript,
在清除一个函数之前，您可以通过词法调用它。
you can lexically call a function before you can clear it.
我可以说&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我明白你的意思了。
I can say &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I see what you mean.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：我可以说foo parent，然后在下面我可以说function foo。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: I can say foo parent, and then below that I can say function foo.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：你的意思不是说var，一些函数名，和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You don't mean to say var, some function name, and
然后在以后找到一个函数。
then later on to find a function.
我明白了，没关系。
I see, nevermind.
这两种说法，
These two statements,
我正在寻找的这两个语句之间没有相似之处。
there's not this parallel between these two statements that I'm looking for.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：所以函数不是变量。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So functions aren't variables.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：不，函数是可以存储在变量中的值。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: No, functions are values that can be stored in variables.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，如果他们有名字的话。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay, if they have a name.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：甚至匿名函数也可以存储在变量中。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Even anonymous functions can be stored in variables.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.